<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
    <channel>
        <title>Jungle Sequencer Blog</title>
        <link>https://junglesequencer.com/blog</link>
        <description>Jungle Sequencer Blog</description>
        <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <docs>https://validator.w3.org/feed/docs/rss2.html</docs>
        <generator>https://github.com/jpmonette/feed</generator>
        <language>en</language>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Beta Program]]></title>
            <link>https://junglesequencer.com/blog/beta-program</link>
            <guid>https://junglesequencer.com/blog/beta-program</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 29 Jan 2024 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hey Everyone 👋, I'm so excited to announce that you can now sign up for the Jungle Sequencer Beta Program.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hey Everyone 👋, I'm so excited to announce that you can now sign up for the Jungle Sequencer Beta Program.</p>
<p>Jungle has been in the works for almost three years now. I've worked so hard to make it the best tool it can be. With
the official release around the corner, I want to get an edge on any bugs or issues I didn't catch.</p>
<p>A tool of this size and complexity is bound to have some bugs. I've done my best to catch them all, but I'm sure there
are some that have slipped through the cracks.</p>
<p>That's where you come in. I need your help to make Jungle the best it can be. If you're interested in joining the beta
program, please fill out <strong><a href="https://forms.gle/55ZSyBrhH8iDoGKK8" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">this form</a></strong>.</p>
<p>I'm looking for developers of all skill levels. Whether you're a beginner or an expert, I want to hear from you. I'm
looking for feedback on:</p>
<ul>
<li>The user interface</li>
<li>The functionality</li>
<li>The documentation</li>
<li>And the overall experience.</li>
</ul>
<p>The beta is a great opportunity to get a sneak peek at Jungle before anyone else. You'll also get to keep the version
you test for <strong>free</strong>.</p>
<p>I'm so excited to see what you all think. I can't wait to hear from you.</p>
<p>Happy coding! 🌴</p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Text Tie - GPT Knowledge File Builder]]></title>
            <link>https://junglesequencer.com/blog/text-tie</link>
            <guid>https://junglesequencer.com/blog/text-tie</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Waddup 👋]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p><strong>Waddup</strong> 👋</p>
<p>This is a little post I wanted to make about a tool I created...</p>
<p>I've been working on a CustomGPT model for Jungle to help developers with any questions they may have. CustomGPT's allow
you to upload knowledge files that help give the model context for the questions developers may ask.</p>
<p>All the docs used to build this site are markdown files, and the CustomGPT can't read from markdown files. This meant I
had to manually convert <strong>EACH AND EVERY</strong> markdown file into a text file. This was a very tedious process and I wanted
to automate it.</p>
<p><strong>My solution:</strong> I created a tool called Text Tie to help me append all my docs together into a single text file that I
can easily upload. It allows me to append files are specific extensions into a single text file. This makes an hour long
process take two minutes.</p>
<p>Feel free to use it if you need, <strong>it's open source and free to use</strong>.</p>
<ul>
<li>Download it <a href="https://github.com/JackaPacka/Text-Tie/releases/tag/Release" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.</li>
</ul>
<p><img loading="lazy" src="https://i.imgur.com/6JtGLyQ.png" alt="Text Tie app" class="img_ev3q"></p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Welcome]]></title>
            <link>https://junglesequencer.com/blog/welcome</link>
            <guid>https://junglesequencer.com/blog/welcome</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 12 Dec 2023 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
            <description><![CDATA[Hey 👋, I'm Jack Randolph, also known as JackaPacka. I'm the creator of Jungle.]]></description>
            <content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Hey 👋, I'm Jack Randolph, also known as JackaPacka. I'm the creator of Jungle.</p>
<p>This is my first time ever blogging. I figured I would use this place to share change logs, announcements, and updates
regarding Jungle. If you're reading this, I can't thank you enough! Honestly, I've never followed another developer's
blog myself, so knowing you're here reading mine is incredibly meaningful to me.</p>
<p>I've been working on Jungle for the past three plus years. It has been a huge passion project for me. I'm so happy
(and quite nervous) to finally get it out into the hands of developers. I cannot wait to see what you all create!</p>
<p>Jungle originally started as a tiny little tool for a game I was working on. I needed a tool that could help me create
dialog trees, missions, boss battles, and cinematics/animations more easily.</p>
<p>I spent only about a week developing the first version of Jungle. It was very bare bones compared to what Jungle is
today. Even being as bare bones as it was, the tool was still <strong>INCREDIBLY</strong> useful. I kept on developing it alongside
my game, and it just got better and better.</p>
<p>Then, I started working on my recreation of the hit game Iron Long inside virtual reality. I used Jungle to handle all
the animations and cinematics in the game. You can check out my remake <a href="https://jackaapacka.itch.io/iron-lung-vr" target="_blank" rel="noopener noreferrer">here</a>.
This proved to me that Jungle could work in a shipped product.</p>
<p>Every aspect of Jungle has been meticulously designed to ensure it's the best tool possible. I truly hope you enjoy
using Jungle as much as I loved creating it!</p>
<p>So long for now,
<br><strong>Jack Randolph</strong></p>]]></content:encoded>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>